[
    {
      "front": "English",
      "back": "Arabic",
      "back_hint": "Pronunciation",
      "Lesson": "1"
    },
    {
      "front": "vocabulary words",
      "back": "المُفْرَدَات",
      "back_hint": "al mofradat"
    },
    {
      "front": "(one) vocabulary word",
      "back": "المُفْرَد",
      "back_hint": "al mofrad"
    },
    {
      "front": "\"formal, written (classical) Arabic\"",
      "back": "الفُصْحَى",
      "back_hint": "al fusha"
    },
    {
      "front": "grammar",
      "back": "القَوَاعِد",
      "back_hint": "al qawa'id"
    },
    {
      "front": "sentence",
      "back": "جُمْلَة",
      "back_hint": "jumla"
    },
    {
      "front": "culture",
      "back": "الثَّقَافَة",
      "back_hint": "aththaqafa"
    },
    {
      "front": "literature",
      "back": "الأَدَب",
      "back_hint": "al adab"
    },
    {
      "front": "really?",
      "back": "واللهِ؟",
      "back_hint": "wallah"
    },
    {
      "front": "United Nations",
      "back": "الأُمَم المُتَّحِدَة",
      "back_hint": "al umam al muttahida"
    },
    {
      "front": "which?",
      "back": "أَيّ؟",
      "back_hint": "ayy"
    },
    {
      "front": "nationality",
      "back": "جِنْسِيَّة",
      "back_hint": "jinsiyya"
    },
    {
      "front": "I study",
      "back": "أَدْرُس",
      "back_hint": "adrus"
    },
    {
      "front": "\"I live, reside\"",
      "back": "أَسْكُن",
      "back_hint": "askun"
    },
    {
      "front": "\"she lives (also, you masc. live)\"",
      "back": "تَسْكُن",
      "back_hint": "taskun"
    },
    {
      "front": "he resides",
      "back": "يَسْكُن",
      "back_hint": "yaskun"
    },
    {
      "front": "year",
      "back": "سَنَة",
      "back_hint": "sana"
    },
    {
      "front": "really? For real?",
      "back": "صَحِيح؟!",
      "back_hint": "sahih"
    },
    {
      "front": "age",
      "back": "عُمْر",
      "back_hint": "umr"
    },
    {
      "front": "\"she works (also, you masc. work)\"",
      "back": "تَعْمَل",
      "back_hint": "ta'mal"
    },
    {
      "front": "he works",
      "back": "يَعْمَل",
      "back_hint": "ya'mal"
    },
    {
      "front": "address",
      "back": "عُنْوَان",
      "back_hint": "'unwan"
    },
    {
      "front": "Egyptian",
      "back": "مِصْرِيّ / مِصْرِيَّة",
      "back_hint": "misriyya"
    },
    {
      "front": "who?",
      "back": "مَن؟",
      "back_hint": "man?"
    },
    {
      "front": "\"area, region\"",
      "back": "مِنْطَقَة",
      "back_hint": "mintaqa"
    },
    {
      "front": "the same",
      "back": "نَفْس الــــ",
      "back_hint": "nafs al"
    },
    {
      "front": "the same university",
      "back": "نَفْس الجَامِعَة",
      "back_hint": "nafs al jami'a"
    },
    {
      "front": "father",
      "back": "وَالِد",
      "back_hint": "walid"
    },
    {
      "front": "my father",
      "back": "وَالِدِي",
      "back_hint": "walidi"
    },
    {
      "front": "mother",
      "back": "وَالِدَة",
      "back_hint": "walida"
    },
    {
      "front": "my mother",
      "back": "وَالِدَتِي",
      "back_hint": "walidati"
    },
    {
      "front": "What? (Question without verb)",
      "back": "ما؟",
      "back_hint": "ma?"
    },
    {
      "front": "What? (Question with verb)",
      "back": "ماذا؟",
      "back_hint": "madha?"
    },
    {
      "front": "Which?",
      "back": "أيّ؟",
      "back_hint": "ayy?"
    },
    {
      "front": "Where?",
      "back": "أينَ",
      "back_hint": "ayna?"
    },
    {
      "front": "How?",
      "back": "كَيف",
      "back_hint": "kayfa?"
    }
  ]
  